

CONTACT



+61 414 367 359



⊠ gellis7@gmail.com

PROFILE

I apply for this position with 4.5 years' experience as a contractor working on multiple projects and 2.5 years as a site engineer at Alcoa's Wagerup Alumina Refinery. Analysing and solving complex problems have been essential skills in my career thus far. From very specialized experience at Honeywell, to a more generalist role in the last 2 years, I have the skillset for this role.

I believe in an inclusive workplace culture and will strive to cultivate positive relationships within the team and organisation. If you select me for this position, I will bring a calm, decisive and open-minded perspective to the role.

SKILLS

- PROCESS CONTROL
- **ANALYSIS**
- **NEGOTIATION**
- PROBLEM SOLVING

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering

2009-2014

University of Western Australia Chemical and Process Engineering First Class Honours

Bachelor of Science

2009-2014

University of Western Australia Applied Mathematics Analytical Chemistry

EXPERIENCE

Process Control Engineer – Alcoa Wagerup

2019-Present

Designed and commissioned new advanced controllers in milling and powerhouse (mills, 25A tanks, boilers and tie)

Significant redesign and rebuild of controllers in precipitation (cooling tower, end tank temperature and classification)

Dynamic non-linear models added to digestor temperature, 30A temperature and washer total solids

Advanced Process Control Engineer - Honeywell

2014-2019

6 Months as control engineer at Alcoa's Pinjarra Alumina Refinery

Design and commissioning of advanced process controllers

- Boiler house, Ma'aden Alumina Refinery
- Mills, Ma'aden Alumina Refinery
- Precipitation, Ma'aden Alumina Refinery
- Washers, Ma'aden Alumina Refinery
- Settlers, Ma'aden Alumina Refinery
- Digestion, Ma'aden Alumina Refinery
- Calcination, Sao Luis Alumina Refinery

Development of simulation software for testing advanced process controllers.